[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
(All characters and organisations in this drama are fictional.)
(Filming with minors followed broadcast guidelines,)
(and generative AI was used in select scenes.)
(Episode 14)
What kind of life have you lived?
For the eight years since you left me,
what kind of life have you lived?
Gyu Rim.
You'll wake Gyeol.
Please close the door.
What happened?
How badly was he beaten that my Sung Wook needs surgery?
- He lost several teeth. - And?
The surgery's because he tore his cartilage when he fell.
Who was it? Who did this to my son?
What, did he run into some gangsters?
It wasn't gangsters, just one person.
I mean, he was beaten up by one guy.
I don't know him.
He said he's one of Sung Wook's seniors who knows him well.
- What? - Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my goodness.
Get up.
Our wedding is only one week away. What do I do, Mother?
I used to do a bit of boxing when I was younger.
Usually, 1 punch would knock out 3 teeth.
Did he really lose six teeth?
If you're...
someone with such a strong punch, you should have held back even more.
You said he's a close acquaintance,
so how could you beat him so mercilessly?
I wasn't beating up a person.
I was beating up an animal.
What?
Gosh, you're not asleep?
Since when...
have you been sitting there like that?
It's okay. It's not a big deal.
Doesn't everyone have a birth secret?
My dad is 160cm tall, and though I've never asked,
it's possible he might not be my real father, you know.
Did you meet with the Chairman?
Did he go all, "I am your father?"
Did he tell you to call him Dad from now on?
Wait a minute.
Come to think of it, how come in your family...
there's a birth secret in every generation?
It's the same with Han Gyeol.
You're just choosing to ignore it.
Han Gyeol is also under suspicion of being your son.
Can you please be quiet?
I thought this stuff only happened in dramas,
but I didn't know birth secrets were this common.
I told you to shut up, you bastard.
"Shut up, you bastard."
If there's anything I can do to help...
Help? My foot.
What could you possibly do to help, Kim Mu Jin?
You can just tell me the truth.
The truth about what?
I'm telling you, I really don't know.
I was away on business, and when I came back,
you had already been born.
They told me the day before was your 100-day celebration.
I even ate the ceremonial rice cakes.
Your daughter was having a baby, so why weren't you at home, Grandpa?
I was out earning money.
Hey, and it's not like your mom asked me...
for permission to have you, did she?
Hey, I have plenty to be frustrated and upset about too.
At my age and with my looks,
I have to hear people call me Grandpa because of you.
You don't like me, do you, Grandpa?
I didn't at first. My stomach.
But what can I do?
You're my own flesh and blood.
If I weren't your flesh and blood with your blood in me,
you'd hate me, right?
What are you talking about? It's the crack of dawn.
Get out. You. Get out of here now.
I can't strain with you in here, you punk.
I'm not your grandson.
So stressful. Hey. Come on, go back to sleep.
You must have woken up and started sleep-talking.
Go get some proper sleep. Go on.
Gyeol, are you in the bathroom?
Hey, Gyu Rim. Get Gyeol out of here, now.
He's sleep-talking like he's wide awake.
So I can finish up. Get out, quick.
Gyeol.
Grandpa is trying to use the restroom.
What were you doing in there?
I was trying to ask who I am.
What do you mean, "who are you?"
You're Grandpa's grandson and my son.
Gyeol.
Don't worry about me.
How can you say that to your mom?
And why do you keep speaking so formally to me?
Why are you suddenly speaking so formally?
- Like some other family's kid. - Because I am.
Gyeol.
And it's because...
you're not my mom, ma'am.
What is he talking about?
Uncles, I need to talk to you.
Uncle. Quick.
What time is it?
A little after five.
What's going on this early?
I'm sorry.
It's just that this is very important to me.
What's so important?
I have a bit of a birth secret.
My mom.
I'm not Han Gyu Rim's son.
What are you talking about?
If you're not her son, are you her daughter?
By any chance, did you see my mom give birth to me?
I didn't see you being born, no. I was in the army.
When I came home on leave later,
I saw you when you were the size of a caterpillar.
So anyway, you didn't see me being born, right?
Wait, what's all this about so early in the morning?
Did you fight with your mom?
Uncle. Youngest uncle.
What?
Uncle, did you see my mom give birth to me?
Did you see my mom give birth to me?
No, I didn't.
See?
There's no one.
Anyone who saw me being born...
Why are you sitting there like that?
Gyeol,
talk to me.
This kid.
Oh, Gyeol. Good morning.
Well...
What?
Hey, what's wrong with Gyeol today?
You didn't really give birth to Gyeol? Seriously?
He's my son.
I'm not asking if he's your son.
I'm asking if you actually gave birth to him.
Yes.
I gave birth to him.
He's my son.
Right. Of course. That makes sense.
Why would you raise a child that isn't yours? Right?
Especially when you were being judged...
for being a single mother...
Seriously...
Where could Gyeol have heard something like that?
Oh, is it because of that silly story...
about kids being found under a bridge?
That must be it, right?
Hey, when you were pregnant with Gyeol,
show him the ultrasound photos.
That'll solve it, right?
What?
- Why... - What's this?
Gosh.
Hey.
Gyeol is your sister's son, right? Tell me the truth.
Dad, are you even my father? Seriously?
Oh, please tell me you're not. Please.
I'm washing my hands of this.
Gyeol.
You don't want to talk to me?
No, I don't, ma'am.
Hoon Tae told you, right?
That Gyu Rim is my daughter.
And that's why...
I was so against you and Seo Hyun getting together.
Yes.
I'm sorry, Mu Jin.
To you,
to Hoon Tae, and to Seo Hyun.
I've done something unforgivable.
How can the world be...
so small.
I just can't believe how small the world is...
As for Gyu Rim,
aren't you sorry for her?
You said you never once saw Gyu Rim...
after your divorce.
That you never contacted her or went to see her.
But you're her mother.
Weren't you curious how your daughter was living...
or what she was growing up to be?
I was curious, but I resisted.
I missed her, but I endured it.
I tried with all my might to forget her and move on.
So that I could survive.
It felt like the only way I could go on living.
I wanted to be devoted to my new family.
Hoon Tae thinks the world of me.
And Seo Hyun, even though she knows I'm not her birth mother,
she never leaves my side.
To Hoon Tae and to Seo Hyun,
I wanted to repay them too.
What about Gyu Rim?
Gyu Rim needed a mother too.
She must have longed for...
a mother's warmth every single day.
Gyu Rim is a strong kid.
She's brave and resilient.
She always pulls through...
and she...
must have endured it. I trust Gyu Rim.
How can you say that? She was just a child.
A child who desperately needed her mother.
Apologise to Gyu Rim.
Even now.
I'm not going to see her.
- No, I can't. - Ma'am.
I'm never going to see her again.
Besides, for Gyu Rim...
she's better off without me.
You're being cruel...
and selfish to the very end.
Yes.
That's right.
I never knew I could be this selfish and cruel.
Where did he go?
Ma'am.
Why are you following me?
I was worried you might skip school.
I don't ditch school, no matter how tough things get.
I know. But I was still worried, just in case.
Ma'am.
Can you please stop calling me that?
Why are you calling me that?
Then should I call you my sister?
My friends already think it's weird how young you look.
They say you look like a pop star.
I am your mom, Gyeol.
I can tell the whole world that I am your mom.
Whatever.
I'm serious.
I'll keep shouting it until you believe me.
But you're a textbook introvert.
You hate being embarrassed more than anything.
I am Gyeol's mom!
I am Han Gyeol's mom!
- I, Han Gyu Rim, am Gyeol's mom! - No, no. Stop it.
- I said stop. - I wouldn't trade...
my son, Han Gyeol, for the entire world.
- No, no. Stop it. - Hello.
Oh, hello. You should get inside.
- Han Gyeol is... - Stop.
the one Han Gyu Rim loves most...
- in this world. - Mom, stop it. Just stop.
Will you believe me now?
Han Gyeol.
Your mom is so cool, Han Gyeol.
I wish I had a cool and pretty mom like you do.
I really do.
Hello, Ms. Kwon.
I'll be heading in now.
Gyeol, listen to your teacher...
and get along with your friends.
I'll take good care of Gyeol, so please don't worry.
Thank you.
Han Gyeol, wait up.
Han Gyeol.
Man, I'm so tired.
This is driving me crazy.
Why won't you agree to a settlement? Why?
Your mom has a lot of money.
Why would I settle when I didn't do anything wrong?
I will never settle.
Just go.
Are you trying to get revenge on me right now?
Are you using everything you've been holding a grudge about...
to get back at me?
I believe in punishment, not revenge.
If I had known what kind of jerk Sung Wook was,
I would have beaten him to a pulp before he ever met you.
Seriously, this is all Han Gyu Rim's fault.
If it weren't for Han Gyu Rim,
I never would've met someone like you.
She's been completely useless my entire life.
Blame the right person.
If it weren't for your sister,
would you even be able to stand on your own two feet right now?
Whatever.
Because of you, my wedding is completely ruined.
With Sung Wook in his condition,
we can't have our wedding or honeymoon.
How are you going to pay for it?
The cancellation fees are astronomical.
So how are you going to pay for it?
I'll pay the fees even if I have to sell my body,
so don't worry.
But as for beating up Sung Wook,
I will never agree to a settlement for that.
Are you serious?
They say birds of a feather flock together.
It's amazing how you two, like identical twins,
found each other.
Think of me as your saviour and call off this wedding.
- This is your last warning. - A saviour? Give me a break.
Fine. Don't settle. Don't you dare settle.
Don't settle, and just go rot in prison,
Jo Heung Sik.
My gosh. What do I do?
No, this is no time for this.
My Heung Sik! Which jail is my Heung Sik in?
Instead of going to the jail, you should settle first.
You have to settle to get Jo Heung Sik out, don't you?
Right, a settlement.
Okay, so where do I go and how do I settle?
You can settle with me.
Recovery will take 20 weeks. He lost 6 teeth.
Surgery, treatment, hospitalization, nursing fees,
compensation for emotional distress,
plus the wedding, reception, and honeymoon,
cancellation fees. You have to pay for it all.
How much is all that?
I hear you have about three more shops...
besides this one.
Just sell one of them.
Darn it. This little vixen...
is talking utter nonsense.
So you're just going to let Jo Heung Sik rot in prison?
Are you going to let your son get a criminal record?
Oh, dear.
Your world is falling apart, isn't it?
I feel like I'm going to go crazy too.
So before this gets out to more people...
Gyeol's Mom was born in March in the Year of the Dog,
and she said her younger sister was born 11 months later...
Pig...
Does that mean you were born in February...
in the Year of the Pig?
Why are you asking for my birth date?
She was right.
The shaman at Wolseongdang...
told me to be very, very careful of someone...
born in February in the Year of the Pig.
Even if they offer you...
the most delicious treat in the world,
she said not to even go near them.
- What is she saying? - In my Heung Sik's fortune,
if he gets close to someone...
born in February in the Year of the Pig,
everything would just go up in flames.
- Ma'am. - Get out. Forget the settlement.
I don't want to speak to someone...
born in February in the Year of the Pig.
Get lost.
Don't you dare hang around my Heung Sik.
Next time, it'll be for attempted murder...
that you and I will have to settle. You hear me?
Where did this "Born in February in the Year of the Pig"...
nonsense come from? Ma'am, you can't lose your mind too.
Are you really going to let your son become a convict?
Go on, get out of here.
Or do I have to take this spinach water...
and splash it on your face?
Darn it, I can't reason with her.
Those born in February in the Year of the Pig...
are terrifying, right? If this wedding gets called off,
I'll just go and marry Jo Heung Sik.
No. That little brat!
(Suragan Side Dishes)
Hey.
Can't you see me?
What are you doing here?
Didn't you go to work?
That Jo Heung Sik...
I didn't come home last night.
You didn't even notice I wasn't home, did you?
You're not a kid.
Do I have to worry about you on top of everything else?
I'm fine with us disowning each other,
but I'm not married yet.
Let's wait until after I'm married to do it.
To make it meaningful.
I'm leaving.
I have a question.
If the mother is Type O,
is it really impossible for her to have a Type AB child?
- What are you talking about? - No, what if the father is Type AB?
Isn't that possible?
Are you trying to show me how clueless you are?
Why am I so stupid?
I can't believe I didn't even know that.
Gyeol isn't your son, is he?
Gyeol called me.
He asked if I knew who his real mom was.
So what did you tell him?
I told him I didn't know.
When I got back from studying abroad,
he had already been born.
Why would you tell him that?
You could've just said that I'm his mom.
I only state the facts.
Wait.
So Gyeol really isn't your son?
Then why are you raising a kid who isn't even yours?
That's enough.
Let's just stop.
Hey.
Who is Gyeol's real mom? What does she do?
You've never even changed one of his diapers.
So shut your mouth.
- Gyeol is my son. - You're insane.
You've completely lost it.
Is charity your talent and self-sacrifice your hobby?
You're not married, but you let them call you a single mom...
and let the whole world judge you.
You don't care about me.
So be consistent and just stay out of it.
You're so annoying.
Weren't the twins enough for you?
Why are you so busy sacrificing yourself for everyone?
Just get government funding and open an orphanage or something.
Seriously.
Why bother waiting for the wedding?
Let's just disown each other right now.
Darn it, did she break my nose?
The back of my head, now the front...
Did you two team up to take me down today?
Hey, Han Gyu Rim.
Darn it.
Have you eaten?
I moved my things out of the house.
(Chairman Jang Hoon Tae)
I'll ask you one last time.
You were just messing with me, right?
You always loved messing with me, Dad.
You're just joking around this time too, right?
I was totally shocked, and I completely fell for it.
So just tell me it's over now.
Tell me the joke is finished.
That I can stop being frozen in place.
I said, stop joking around.
This kind of joke isn't funny. I absolutely hate it.
Listen to me.
I'm going to step away from managing the company for a while.
I don't know if it will be for 1 year or 2.
In the meantime, your mother and I will go...
to our farm on Jeju Island and rest,
until you've calmed down and sorted out your feelings.
So you're serious, then?
After making this huge mess, you're just going to run away?
Like a coward?
I don't know how Mom can stand you.
How can she be with someone as loathsome as you?
Eat with you, sleep in the same bed,
talk with you, and breathe the same air?
My mom must not be human.
Divorce her first.
My mom is too soft-hearted to say it,
so I'm saying it for her.
Divorce her and let her go.
Since you're the one at fault,
you should sign over all your assets to her too.
Seo Hyun.
That's what I came to say.
If you move your things out, I'll move back in and live with Mom.
(Chairman Hong Ok Seon)
Good.
Very good.
Hey, this is all great,
but what's the point of having such a fantastic product...
if the marketing that supports it isn't fantastic as well?
So, is there still no word from that artist, Joel?
No.
I went to the address listed on his website in person,
but he's the type who comes in whenever he feels like it,
so meeting him isn't easy.
I've also sent him DMs on social media,
but he hasn't replied.
His employees...
say that hardly anyone there has even seen their boss's face.
Well, this will be a problem even if we land the project.
If he's that eccentric, how can we possibly work with him?
Yes? What is it?
You have a visitor, Chairman.
Who is it?
Well, I'll see myself out then.
You met with Hoon Tae, didn't you?
He was spouting such ridiculous nonsense,
that I told him to get psychiatric help...
and then we'd talk.
I'm sorry to have put you in such an awkward position.
I mean,
were you conned by some guy who looks like my Mu Jin?
If you don't approve of my Mu Jin,
you could have just been honest with me and said so.
Whose idea was this anyway?
Does Jang Hoon Tae need to be committed to a hospital?
I'm sorry.
Even if I had ten mouths...
I have no excuse.
How dare you do this to a catch like my son?
For Seo Hyun's late mother's sake,
I treated you with every courtesy I could muster.
But how dare you.
You don't even know your place.
How could you treat my son like that...
and reject him so disgracefully?
I'm sorry, Chairman.
Why so quiet all of a sudden?
Go on. Glare at me and say it out loud.
Say, "Over my dead body will I accept Mu Jin."
Go on and drive me crazy.
You know what?
For Seo Hyun's sake, I...
I'm done with this. Okay?
Tell Hoon Tae to delete my number.
And tell him that our long relationship ends here.
Relay that message.
Han Gyu Rim is my daughter.
What? Who is?
The girl Mu Jin used to date.
The one you treated like a gold digger.
That girl.
The one I left behind when I got divorced.
She's my eldest daughter.
What are you talking about right now? What?
That's why I was so against...
Seo Hyun and Mu Jin getting together.
For not knowing my place.
Wait a minute.
Look here, Yoon Hee.
Hoon Tae feared...
she'd refuse to see me again,
so he took all the blame.
Oh my goodness.
- Please have a seat over there. - Okay.
Ma'am, I'd like a bottle of makgeolli.
Okay.
Hello.
Do you know me?
You don't know me?
(Danim-Gil Kalguksu)
So you're the long tooth grouper lady.
Right?
No.
Your makgeolli.
No, I just thought you looked a lot like her...
I really didn't think it could be you.
I was just coming from a wedding.
Since you know each other, why not sit together?
Okay? We're out of tables.
Please, have a seat.
- Okay. - Go on, sit down.
So...
Please be honest with me.
What is it that you do?
I run a sashimi place.
No, you used to run that place.
I reopened it. I have to make a living.
I don't think so.
You have a completely different aura.
You have the air of a wealthy corporation chairman's wife.
My younger sibling runs a dry cleaner,
so I borrowed the nicest clothes they had.
The food at the wedding must have been disappointing.
You even ordered makgeolli.
Something truly unbelievable happened.
You too? Me too.
Want to make a bet?
On whose story is more unbelievable?
You're on.
Actually, no. I don't even want to talk about it.
Oh, come on. Give it a try.
Fifty dollars, all in.
Wait, let me.
My son's ex-girlfriend...
and the girl he just started seeing...
have the same mother.
I could not believe it. Seriously.
Could you say that one more time? I am not following.
Oh, forget it. I am not saying it twice.
I...
raised him thinking he was my grandchild,
but he isn't my grandchild.
This kid messaged me again.
Asking me to tell him about his birth secret.
Calls, texts, messages, nonstop.
I honestly have no idea.
The 50 dollars is yours.
Why are you staring at me like that? Want me to pour you one?
No, it is not that.
The way you down your drink in one shot...
looked kind of cool,
and I could not help but keep watching.
What? Are you hitting on me right now?
No. Am I crazy? Come on.
I am absolutely sick and tired of women.
Even if you tried your hardest to seduce me,
I would never fall for it.
I would never try to seduce you,
but if I did, you would fall for it.
No, I would not.
When it comes to women,
I'm completely fed up.
Have you been fooled your whole life?
Want to make a bet?
Every time I say something, you want to bet? Really?
Bet too much and you will end up with nothing overnight.
Like me.
Deal?
Mu Jin.
Hey, you are here?
Is it okay if I call you casually when we are outside?
Of course.
What do you want to eat?
Maybe in a bit.
Have a seat first.
Okay.
If I asked you to tell me how Gyu Rim has been doing...
since she broke up with me until recently,
like the whole story of the past eight years,
would that be too much?
No.
What took you so long to ask?
I have always been ready to tell you.
It is going to be a long story, though.
Let me go grab some ice cream.
Give me your card.
Gyeol has my sister completely freaking out right now.
He says he needs to know his birth secret,
and he's been keeping everyone up since this morning.
I see.
Gyeol came to see me too.
I was never good at school, so I do not really know,
but is it really true that a Type O mother...
cannot have a Type AB child?
Like, regardless of the father's blood type?
I thought my sister gave birth to Gyeol.
She even showed me a photo of the baby in her belly.
A photo?
She showed you an ultrasound?
- Yes. - When?
Eight years ago, when I was in elementary school.
Now that I think about it, it was an ultrasound photo,
and she only showed it to me. She said it was her baby.
She even had a nickname for the baby.
What was it...
I remember.
Hope.
My sister even had a baby bump this big.
So I thought...
maybe you were Gyeol's dad.
So what happened?
My sister even went to the hospital to give birth.
Could it be...
the babies were switched at the hospital?
Start the car.
Just take me somewhere. Anywhere.
Want to just run away?
Forget about family and everything...
and let's just live together.
Let's go somewhere no one will find us...
and just be together, just the two of us. Okay?
I said let's run away. So why did you just bring here?
Have you eaten?
Or, well,
should I get you a sandwich or something?
Be honest. You were relieved, weren't you?
You were just dragging yourself along...
out of obligation,
and when you heard, "You two have to end it here,"
you were secretly thrilled, weren't you?
You know, I always had this weird, nagging feeling.
That we...
weren't going to make it all the way.
I had a strange feeling like that.
Let's just get a meal every now and then.
If you want to eat something good,
call me anytime.
Every now and then?
So now you only want to see me every now and then?
Yes.
Let's only see each other every now and then.
This is sad.
It's so unfair.
We never even got to do anything.
We never even went to the movies once.
We never went on a trip.
We never got couple rings. We never even kissed once.
Where are you going?
I'll take you.
No mercy at all.
You're not giving me any room at all, are you?
I'll start the car and wait.
Don't you dare date anyone else!
Don't fall in love with anyone...
and just die alone your whole life! Got it?
Where will you go after you drop me off?
To work.
Go to Han Gyu Rim.
I was just holding you back, so you couldn't go to her.
I don't know if it's sincerity or hypocrisy,
but think of this as my gift to you for doing your best for me.
Go to her, even if it's now.
And this is a favour.
If you two get back together,
I want you to completely disappear.
Go somewhere I will never hear anything about you two again.
Disappear without a trace.
Is it okay for you to be out here, away from your store?
Gyeol...
Gyeol isn't coming out.
All the other kids are coming out,
but Gyeol isn't.
Snap out of it.
I've never seen you...
this distraught before.
If you act like this,
Gyeol will get more confused and anxious.
Okay.
I'll pull myself together.
I'll wait for Gyeol, so you go back to the store. Go on.
You are not this irresponsible.
Why are you being like this? This isn't like you, Han Gyu Rim.
Hey.
Okay.
Please take good care of Gyeol.
I will.
Gyu Oh.
Gyeol...
He's my son.
I know.
He means more to me than my own life.
Hey.
I know.
Gyeol.
Han Gyeol.
Grade 1, Class 2, Han Gyeol.
Gyeol. Han...
Uncle.
Gyeol.
What are you doing at my school?
I came to pick you up.
Why? Are you worried I'm going to act out?
No, I wanted to buy you something good to eat.
That's okay. Ms. Kwon said she'd treat me.
- Let's go, Ms. Kwon. - Okay.
Are you uncomfortable?
What?
That we're eating pizza while my uncle is standing outside?
Does that make you uncomfortable?
No.
Well, I feel uncomfortable.
But even so,
I don't want to talk to my family at all.
Gyeol,
I know you're very confused and shocked.
But constantly avoiding your mom and your family like this...
isn't the right thing to do.
You don't have school tomorrow,
so you and your mom should take a trip somewhere nice.
You can ask her what you're curious about...
and have her explain.
Your mom is the best mom ever.
I've met Da Som's mom, Jae Beom's mom,
I've met them all.
But I've never met a mom as devoted...
and loving toward her child as Gyeol's Mom.
It's true.
Ms. Kwon, I want to go. I don't want pizza anymore.
Gyeol.
Han Gyeol.
Ma'am, your bill?
Talk to me for a minute.
I have nothing to say.
Well, I have something to say.
I don't want to hear anything you have to say.
Wow, you've really developed an attitude.
You said you don't know anything.
You said you didn't see my mom give birth to me.
I didn't see my mom give birth to me either.
I need time to think.
Tell that to Ms. Han Gyu Rim, too.
Ms. Han Gyu Rim?
Do you have any idea what state your mom is in because of you?
Gyeol, you can't just say whatever you want.
Calm down, Gyeol's Uncle.
Goodbye, Ms. Kwon.
Hey, where are you going? Home is the other way.
I'm not going to my house.
I'm going to Mr. Mu Jin's.
Why are you going there?
Why does a little kid have to cause so much trouble?
How can you act just like him?
Gyeol may be precocious, but he's still just a child.
If there's someone Gyeol feels he can lean on,
you should let him.
As long as you can trust them.
I never thought we'd meet like this.
You don't recognise me?
Han Gyu Oh. You really don't remember?
I don't.
I've erased all my memories of it.
So,
Gyeol's Uncle, please pretend you don't know me either...
if we ever happen to meet again.
Gyu Rim.
Where's Gyeol?
I saw him,
but he went to Mr. Kim Mu Jin's place.
Gyu Seo told me about Mr. Kim Mu Jin.
Anyway,
Gyeol's teacher said that...
if there's someone Gyeol feels he can lean on,
we should just let him.
Who is Gyeol, really?
Is he really not your son?
Then why did you raise him?
Leave.
I respect your privacy, and us living our own lives is fine,
but we're still family.
Whose son Gyeol is,
why you raised a child that isn't yours,
shouldn't you at least be able to tell me that?
Gyeol is my son, Gyu Oh.
No matter what happens,
he is my son.
Gyeol.
What are you doing out here?
Why did you leave me behind?
Do you think I'm a baby?
That doesn't mean I can give you coffee.
Did you come straight here without going home?
Yes.
Did you tell your mom you were coming to see me?
My uncle probably told her.
Oh, really?
Well, that's good.
Am I bothering you?
No. Hey, what kind of question is that?
But it can't be helped.
I have nowhere else to go but here.
Until I find my birth mom.
No matter what anyone says,
your mom always said you were her biological son.
But no one saw my mom give birth to me.
Mister.
Yes?
Instead of milk,
could I get something to eat?
You must be hungry. I'll make you something right away.
What do you want to eat?
Kimchi fried rice.
Hey,
Han Gyeol, you really are your mom's son.
(Geumje Police Station)
Oh, Heung Sik.
Why did you agree to a settlement?
I didn't do anything wrong.
What do you mean you did nothing wrong?
After what you did to that person,
- you did nothing wrong? - Hey, that hurts.
How much did you settle for?
It cost a fortune. Now what?
That's it. Give me that hand of yours...
- so you don't use it recklessly. - Seriously, what gives?
I need to teach that hand of yours a lesson.
Did you tell Gyu Rim?
We have to make sure Gyu Rim never finds out.
Are you in any position to be worrying about her family?
Whose fault is it that we're in this mess?
I don't care about tenant protection.
I'm kicking her family out now,
- and don't you try to stop me. - I dare you to kick them out.
The shared bathroom broke because of your mom's poop.
- I'll post it for everyone to see. - You're unbelievable.
Don't you have a conscience?
My conscience won't let me pretend I don't...
What do you want?
Truth and apology.
Truth and apology, my foot.
I can't believe I gave birth to a snitch...
and ate seaweed soup.
I'll confess that I was the one who did it,
and I'll pay for all the repairs,
so don't you dare kick Gyu Rim's family out.
Fine.
Go ahead, burn the whole place down.
It said if you're involved with someone...
born in February in the Year of the Pig,
all heck will break loose. Right.
Go ahead, burn the whole place down.
What are you talking about?
Who was born in February of the Year of the Pig?
That bastard, Jo Heung Sik.
Everyone told me to be careful around him.
He can't stand to see others do well,
and he gets so jealous.
He's a notorious couple-breaker in our circle.
They even told me not to associate with him.
Darn it.
Am I crazy? Am I out of my mind?
The woman I'm going to marry is less than 3m away,
so why would I kiss a stranger?
Sung Wook, you can't chew apples, can you?
Gyu Young, you're the only one for me.
Really.
What do I have to do for you to believe that I'm innocent?
Should I just drop dead right here in front of you?
Why would you die? Just don't do it again.
You don't believe me.
You can't believe me.
If that's all the faith you have in me,
then let's just call it off.
Let's call the whole thing off.
What is this?
Is she crazy? Darn it.
Gyu Young...
We're not having a wedding.
I was wrong.
I was so wrong.
No, listen, this...
I don't even remember this happening.
My friends threw me a bachelor party,
and they kept making me drink.
Let's skip the ceremony and just take pictures.
In a wedding dress and tuxedo.
What?
So does that mean you'll marry me?
We'll tell the guests we've decided to donate the wedding money...
and say it in style.
Gyu Young, you really are amazing...
Once the community service center opens tomorrow,
we're going to register our marriage.
You just have to sign it.
I'll go by myself.
If you want to have an affair,
go ahead whenever you want without worrying about me.
Then I won't have to worry about you...
and can have an affair too. So, we're good, right?
I was always curious what it's like to have a marriage for show.
Let's give it a try.
It'll be a lot of fun.
(Here Lies My Hope)
(Incoming Call)
It's Hye Jeong.
Gyu Rim.
No matter how much I thought about it,
you're the only person I could think of.
Something's come up for me, and I just can't raise my baby.
I'd be so grateful if you could raise him along with your child,
but if you can't, please take him to an orphanage for me.
I'm so sorry. Please do this for me, Gyu Rim.
(Baby Box)
She's abandoning you...
How can you not even cry?
You're breaking my heart.
Oh, my.
There we go. Okay, all done.
Come on, Han Gyeol. You can do it.
Oh, you can roll over.
Go, Han Gyeol.
Oh, did you roll over?
Lemon.
Mom.
Mom?
Did you just say Mom?
I'm Mom.
I'm your mom. I'm Gyeol's Mom.
Where are you going?
I heard Gyeol is with you.
I was actually just about to call you.
Again,
I am so sorry.
I'm about to wash Gyeol up and put him to bed.
I'm so sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Have you been crying?
No.
Where are you right now?
Where are you?
I'm sorry.
Well, as for Gyeol,
my brother is going to pick him up tomorrow morning.
If you could just send me the address...
Gyu Rim, where are you?
I'm coming to you now.
I'm on my way to you. Where are you?
(Love on the Menu)
Your mom loves you so much. Why do you make her so upset?
I don't know why, but I just keep getting angry.
I went to the community center and registered our marriage.
We didn't just agree to date. We're dating now.
Today is our first day.
Let's stop playing games.
You said you didn't care who it was.
You know I like your mom, right?
- When did you start liking her? - Before you were born.
I'm going to tell him the truth.
- But I'm a little scared. - I can wait all night.
Take your time.